Sam B. Hall, Jr. Papers, Inclusive: 1943-2005, undated Bulk: 1976-1985
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1965-1985, undated; 8
  - Bills, 1968-1985; 2
    - Establishment of a Select Committee on Narcotics Abuse and Control, H.R.65, 1979 January 24 (Box 333, Folder 21)
    - Expenses for House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, H.R.96, 1979 February 5 (Box 333, Folder 22)
    - Fair Trade Enforcement, H.R.3442, 1979 April 4 (Box 333, Folder 23)
    - Federal Civil Defense Act of 1950, H.R.4086, 1979 May 14 (Box 333, Folder 24)
    - Federal Meat Inspection Act, H.R.3881, 1979 (Box 333, Folder 25)
    - Fire Ants, H.R.3687, 1979 April 24 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Free Preventive Dental Care, H.R.6205, 1979 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Gasoline Price Controls, H.R.90, 1979 February 1 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Geriatric Centers, H.R.4015, 1979 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Grand Ole Opry Certificate, H.R.1913, 1979 June 30 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Interest Income for People Over 62, H.R.6290, 1979 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Internal Revenue Code, H.R. 3561, 1979 April 10 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - Internal Revenue Code of 1954, H.R.3883, 1979 May 2 (Box 334, Folder 8)
    - Iran, H.R. 491, 1979 November 26 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Israeli--Egyptian Peace Treaty, H.J.Res.347, 1979 May 30 (Box 334, Folder 10)
    - John Wayne, H.R.3767, 1979 April 26 (Box 334, Folder 11)
    - Joint Committee on Internal Security, H.J.Res.128, 1979 January 22 (Box 334, Folder 12)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Reform Act, 1979 (Box 525 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - MIA in SE Asia, H.Con.Res.10, 1979 January 15 (Box 334, Folder 13)
    - Mineral Leasing Act of 1920, H.R.4058, 1979 (Box 334, Folder 14)
    - National Diabetes Week, H.J.Res.209, 1979 February 15 (Box 334, Folder 15)
    - National Energy Self-Sufficiency Act, H.R. 4484, 1979 June 15 (Box 334, Folder 16)
    - National Enterprise Day, H.J.Res.229, 1979 February 26 (Box 334, Folder 17)
    - National Family Week, H.J.Res.68, 1979 January 15 (Box 334, Folder 18)
    - National Family Week, H.J.Res.118, 1979 January 18 (Box 334, Folder 19)
    - National Lupus Week, H.J.Res.19, 1979 January 15 (Box 334, Folder 20)
    - National Meals on Wheels Week, H.J.Res.238, 1979 March 5 (Box 334, Folder 21)
    - National Park Service, H.R.5712, 1979 (Box 334, Folder 22)
    - Panama Canal Treaties, H.Con.Res.75, 1979 March 15 (Box 334, Folder 23)
    - Peace Development Fund for Middle East, H.Con.Res.85, 1979 March 22 (Box 334, Folder 24)
    - Price Supports, H.J.Res.144, 1979 January 23 (Box 334, Folder 25)
    - Public School Attendance, H.J.Res.74, 1979 January 15 (Box 334, Folder 26)
    - Reduction in Federal Civilian Work Force, H.R.4400, 1979 June 8 (Box 334, Folder 27)
    - For the Relief of David J. Thomas, H.R.5219, 1979 September 7 (Box 334, Folder 28)
    - Repeal Section 506 of the Communications Act of 1934, H.R.4892, 1979 July 20 (Box 334, Folder 29)
    - Small Business Act, H.R.4011, 1979 May 8 (Box 334, Folder 30)
    - Social Security Act, Title II, H.R.3635, 1979 April 9 (Box 334, Folder 31)
    - Social Security Act, Title II, H.R.3992, 1979 May 8 (Box 334, Folder 32)
    - Soft Drink Products, H.R.3567, 1979 (Box 334, Folder 33)
    - Supreme Court Rules, H.R.4712, 1979 July 24 (Box 334, Folder 34)
    - Transfer of Forest Service and Farmers Home Administration, H.Res.187, 1979 March 28 (Box 334, Folder 35)
    - Transfer of Forest Service and Farmers Home Administration, H. Res. 225, 1979 April 10 (Box 334, Folder 36)
    - US Air Force Academy 25th Anniversary, H.Con.Res.90, 1979 March 29 (Box 334, Folder 37)
    - US Space Observance, H.J.Res.353, 1979 June 5 (Box 334, Folder 38)
    - Veterans, H.R.3892, 1979 May 2 (Box 334, Folder 39)
    - Veterans’ Obligated Period of Service Completion Act, H.R.4367, 1979 June 7 (Box 334, Folder 40)
    - Amend Patent and Trademark Laws, H.R.6933, 1980 March -September (Box 334, Folder 41)
    - Amend Tariff Schedules, H.R.7709, 1980 July 1 (Box 334, Folder 42)
    - Amend the Tariff Schedules, H.R.7802, 1980 July 23 (Box 334, Folder 43)
    - American Hostages in Iran, Postage Stamp, H.C.R.379, 1980 July 2 (Box 334, Folder 44)
    - Balancing Federal Budget in 1981, R.Res.525, 1980 April 23 (Box 334, Folder 45)
    - Calendar for Congressional Budget Act, R.Res.615, 1980 March 19 (Box 334, Folder 46)
    - Changes in CHAMPUS, H.R.7536, 1980 June 10 (Box 334, Folder 47)
    - Congressional Budget Act of 1974, Revenue Reconciliation Act, S.2939, 1980 July 2 (Box 334, Folder 48)
    - Constitution, Citizens for Constitutional Government, 1980 (Box 334, Folder 49)
    - Criminal Code, 1980 (Box 334, Folder 50)
    - Criminal Code Revision Act, H.R.6915, 1980 March 25 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Designating July 18, 1980 as National POW-MIA Recognition Day, H.J.Res.507 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Education for Undocumented Alien Children, Impact Aid Act, H.R.8053, 1980 August 25 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Education of Cuban and Haitian Refugees, Education Assistance Act, H.R.7859, 1980 July 29 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Equal Access to Justice Act, H.R.6336, 1980 January 29 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Extend Duty Free Treatment to Certain Freight Containers, H.R.7660, 1980 June 25 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Federal Criminal Code, 1980 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Federal Judgeships, R.Res.693, 1980 June 3 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Language Studies, H.C.R.301, 1980 March 12 (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - Hazardous Materials Transportation and Independent Safely Board, H.R.7103, 1980 April 22 (Box 335, Folder 10)
    - The Hover Craft Skirt Tariff Act, H.R.6750, 1980 March 10, September 22 (Box 335, Folder 11)
    - Immigration and Nationality Act Amendments, H.R.7273, 1980 May 6, Sept. 5 (Box 335, Folder 12)
    - International Development Association African Development Bank, H.R.6811, 1980 March 13, May 16 (Box 335, Folder 13)
    - Internal Revenue Code, H.R. 7348, 1980 May 14 (Box 335, Folder 14)
    - Internal Revenue Code, H.R. 7533, 1980 June 10 (Box 335, Folder 15)
    - Japan-US. Trade, H.Con.Res.376, 1980 June 25 (Box 335, Folder 16)
    - Military Construction, Authorization Act of 1981, S.2333, 1980 February 26 (Box 335, Folder 17)
    - Motor Carrier Act, H.R.6418, 1980 May 21 (Box 335, Folder 18)
    - National Debt, H.J.Res.14, 1980 (Box 335, Folder 19)
    - Provide for Reconciliation Pursuant to Section 3 of the First Concurrent Resolution “Omnibus Reconciliation on the Budget for...1981, H.R.7765, Act of 1980., 1980 July 21 (Box 335, Folder 20)
    - Red Oak Tree for World Peace, H.Con.Res.436, 1980 May (Box 335, Folder 21)
    - Resource Conservation and Development, H.R.6664, 1980 February 28 (Box 335, Folder 22)
    - Royalty Owner Exemption from Crude Oil Windfall Profit Tax, H.R.7348, 1980 May 21 (Box 335, Folder 23)
    - Soft Drink Inter-Brand Competition Act. S.598, 1980 May 19 (Box 335, Folder 24)
    - Teacher Day, USA, H.J.Res.267, 1980 (Box 335, Folder 25)
    - Windfall Profit Tax on Crude Oil, H.R.3919, 1980 April 2 (Box 335, Folder 26)
    - Windfall Profit Tax Reference Material, H.R. 1064, 1980 (Box 335, Folder 27)
    - Agriculture, Farm Bill, 1981 (Box 335, Folder 28)
    - Budget, 1981 (Box 335, Folder 29)
    - Court Recordings, S1700, 1981 (Box 335, Folder 30)
    - Coal, Synthetic Fuel, Facility Survey, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Davis-Bacon, Information Packet, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Davis-Bacon Act, Opinion Ballot, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Davis-Bacon Act, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Drug Enforcement, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Economic, Effects of Sea Grant, 1981 March 26 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Federal Aviation Regulations, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Hobbs Act, Constituent Correspondence S.613, H.R.3047, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Horse Racing, Corrupt Practices Act, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - Illegal Aliens, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - Justice Assistance Act, H.R. 4481 (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - Justice Assistance Act, H.R. 4481 (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - MIA, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 13)
    - Minimum Wage, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 336, Folder 14)
    - National Softball Week, H.J.Res.279, 1981 June 8 (Box 336, Folder 15)
    - Letter Carriers, 1981-1982 (Box 336, Folder 16)
    - Agriculture, Blossom Farm Meeting, 1982 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Milk, 1982 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1982 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Coal, Policy Issues, 1982 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Federal Trade Commission Authorization, Correspondence, 1982 September-October (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Form Letters Sent to Hall, 1982-1984 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - PAC Survey, 1982 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - School Prayer, S.J. Res. 72, 1982 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Tax Increase, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - Tax Increase, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - Agent Orange, 1983 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Agriculture, Dairy, 1983 (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture, Farm Price and Income Support Programs, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Releases, 1983 January 11 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, Blossom Farm Meeting, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, Milk, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, Honey, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, Publications, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, 1983 January 14 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Automotive Products Act, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - Budget Process Reform, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Central America, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - Constituent Correspondence and Opinion Ballots, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 12)
    - Cubans, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 13)
    - Drug, DEA, Notebook A, Articles, Notes, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 14)
    - Drugs, DEA, Notebook B, Hearing, 1983 May 24 (Box 338, Folder 15)
    - Drugs, DEA, Notebook, Statement of Francis M. Mullen, Jr., 1983 (Box 338, Folder 16)
    - Drugs, DEA, Notebook, Overview, 1983 (Box 338, Folder 17)
    - Drugs, DEA, Notebook, Morning Session, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Drugs, DEA, Notebook, Afternoon Session, Coast Guard, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Drugs, DEA, Notebook, Hearing, 1983 June 8 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Drugs, DEA, Notebook, Customs, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Drugs, DEA, Notebook, Publications, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Fair Trade in Steel Pipe and Tube Products Act, H.R.2299, S.1035, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Immigration, Telephone Verification, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Motor Carriers, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Nonprofit Organizations, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Social Security reform, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - State Justice Institute Act, H.R.4145, 1983 (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - Steel, 1983 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Blossom Farm Meeting, Pesticides, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - Armed Career Criminal Act, H.R.6248, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - Asbestos, 1984 June (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Bail Reform Act, H.R. 5865, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - Bankruptcy, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - Brinks Robbery Trial, H.R.5763, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - Concrete Block and Brick, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - Courts, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - Copyright, H.R. 3419 (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 340, Folder 12)
    - Copyright, H.R. 3419 (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 340, Folder 13)
    - Delaware Basin, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 14)
    - Drug Penalty Act, H.R. 4901, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 15)
    - Education Committee, Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 16)
    - Education Committee, Labor, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 17)
    - Elementary, Secondary, & Vocational Ed, 1984 (Box 340, Folder 18)
    - Education & Labor Committee (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 340, Folder 19)
    - Education & Labor Committee (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Education & Labor Committee (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - Farmers, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Immigration Issues, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Activity, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Veto, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - National Federation of Independent Business, Results of Mandate Ballot 452, 1984 February (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - Notes, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - Postal Service, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - Railroad, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - Steel (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 341, Folder 11)
    - Steel (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 341, Folder 12)
    - Steel, Lone Star Steel Letter, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 13)
    - Steel, Annual Report of Congressional Steel Caucus, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 14)
    - Telecommunications Act, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 15)
    - Tax Reform Act, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 16)
    - Technical Amendments to the Federal Court Improvements Act, 1984 (Box 341, Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Contents in Large Envelope Inside Blossom Farm Meeting, 1984 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - VA Land Board, 1984 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - Veterans, 1984 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - Voting, 1984 September 5 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - African Drought Fact Sheet, 1985 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, Blossom Farm Meeting, Milk, 1985 (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Air Defense, 1985 (Box 342, Folder 7)
    - Articles, 1985 (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1985 (Box 342, Folder 9)
    - IRS Mileage Log Requirement on Farm Vehicles, 1985 February (Box 342, Folder 10)
    - IRS Regulations on Record keeping for Business Use of Automobiles, 1985 February (Box 342, Folder 11)
    - Research & Development Tax Credit. “The Need for a Permanent Tax Credit for Industrial Research and Development” H.R.118, 1985 February (Box 342, Folder 12)
    - Taxation on Health Insurance, Pension, etc., 1985 March (Box 342, Folder 13)
    - Texas Homesteading Act, 1985 March (Box 342, Folder 14)
    - Tax, 1985 (Box 342, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1984, undated; 3
    The Correspondence subseries consists of constituent letters concerning general legislative issues. The original filing system, which arranged incoming mail according to categories assigned by staff, has been preserved. One copy of the office filing handbook is also included. Letters were assigned to a classification number, (e.g.., campaign reform was GD204) to facilitate responding and counting. Categories were apparently developed and assigned based on need, therefore the material is neither alphabetical nor chronological. Mass printed opinion mail, such as post cards, is also included. Only sample copies have been retained along with a count of number received. The subseries is dated 1978-1982, and in good condition.
    - The Filing Handbook, Undated (Box 342, Folder 16)
    - Air Transportation (1 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 342, Folder 17)
    - Air Transportation (2 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Busing, 1978-1979 (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Child Care, 1978 (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Child, International Year of the, 1978-1979 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Civil Service (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - Civil Service (2 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - Debt Collection, 1978-1981 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - Economy, 1978-1981 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - Energy (1 of 12), 1979-1980 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Energy (2 of 12), 1979-1980 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Energy (3 of 12), 1979-1980 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Energy (4 of 12), 1979-1980 (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Energy (5 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - Energy (6 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - Energy (7 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Energy (8 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - Energy (9 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 345, Folder 3)
    - Energy, (10 of 12), 1979 (Box 345, Folder 4)
    - Energy, (11 of 12), 1979 (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - Energy, (12 of 12), 1979 (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Energy, Coal (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Energy, Coal (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Energy, Gas, 1978-1981 (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Energy, Solar, 1978-1981 (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Energy, Department of, 1979-1980 (Box 346, Folder 6)
    - Energy, Department of (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 346, Folder 7)
    - Energy, Department of (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 346, Folder 8)
    - Energy, Wind, 1978 (Box 346, Folder 9)
    - Energy Bill, H.R. 6831, 1978 (Box 346, Folder 10)
    - Energy, Gasoline Rationing, 1978-1980 (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Energy, Alcohol Fuels, 1976-1979 (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Environment, 1978-1980 (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - Federal, Marshall Court, 1980-1981 (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Federal Bureaucracy, 1978-1981 (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - Federal Retirement (1 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - Federal Retirement (2 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - Federal Retirement (3 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 347, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1979 (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Affairs (1 of 3), 1977-1981 (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Affairs (2 of 3), 1977-1981 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Affairs (3 of 3), 1977-1981 (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Aid, 1979-1981 (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Forestry (1 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - Forestry (2 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - Forestry (3 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - Franchises, 1978 (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - Freight Rates, 1981 (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - Gun Control (1 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 349, Folder 7)
    - Gun Control (2 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 350, Folder 1)
    - Gun Control (3 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - Gun Control, Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - Gun Control, Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - Gun Control, Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - Gun Control, Black Powder, 1978 (Box 351, Folder 2)
    - Health Care (1 of 5), 1978-1979 (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - Health Care (2 of 5), 1978-1979 (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - Health Care (3 of 5), 1978-1979 (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - Health Care (4 of 5), 1978-1979 (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - Health Care (5 of 5), 1978-1979 (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - Health Care, Hospital Cost Containment, 1978-1981 (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - Health Insurance, 1979 (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - House Reform, 1980 (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - Illegal Aliens, 1976-1980 (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - Illegal Aliens, Cuban/Haitian Refugees, 1980 (Box 352, Folder 6)
    - Judiciary Committee (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 352, Folder 7)
    - Judiciary Committee (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 352, Folder 8)
    - Judiciary Committee, General, 1976 (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - Judiciary Committee (1 of 5), 1979-1980 (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - Judiciary Committee (2 of 5), 1979-1980 (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - Judiciary Committee (3 of 5), 1979-1980 (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - Judiciary Committee (4 of 5), 1979-1980 (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - Judiciary Committee (5 of 5), 1979-1980 (Box 353, Folder 6)
    - Judiciary, Private Bills, 1978-1980 (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - Judiciary, New Judgeships, 1978 (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - Judiciary, Immigration/Aliens Bills (1 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - Judiciary, Immigration/Aliens Bills (2 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - Judiciary, Immigration/Aliens Bills (3 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - Judiciary, Lobby Reform, 1978-1980 (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - Judiciary, Products Liability, 1978 (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - Judiciary, Victim Compensation, 1979 (Box 354, Folder 8)
    - Judiciary, Criminal Code Revision (1 of 3), 1978-1980 (Box 354, Folder 9)
    - Judiciary, Criminal Code Revision (2 of 3), 1978-1980 (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - Judiciary, Criminal Code Revision (3 of 3), 1978-1980 (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - Judiciary, Diversity Jurisdiction, 1979 (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - Judiciary, Patent Law, 1980 (Box 355, Folder 4)
    - Judiciary, 5th Circuit Split, 1980 (Box 355, Folder 5)
    - Labor Unions, 1978 (Box 355, Folder 6)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), 1979-1980 (Box 355, Folder 7)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), 1980 (Box 355, Folder 8)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), 1979 (Box 355, Folder 9)
    - MIA’s, 1978-1980 (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - Mine Safety, 1977-1978 (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - Minimum Wage, 1978-1980 (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 6), 1978-1980 (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 6), 1979-1980 (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - General (3 of 6), 1979-1980 (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - General (4 of 6), 1979-1980 (Box 356, Folder 7)
    - General (5 of 6), 1979-1980 (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - General (6 of 6), 1979-1980 (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence (Civil & Equal Rights) (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 357, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence (Civil & Equal Rights) (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 357, Folder 4)
    - Panama (1 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 357, Folder 5)
    - Panama (2 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 357, Folder 6)
    - Panama (3 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 357, Folder 7)
    - Post Office (1 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 357, Folder 8)
    - Post Office (2 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - Post Office (3 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - Post Office, 9-digit Zip Code, 1980-1981 (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - Postal Service Training, 1981 (Box 358, Folder 4)
    - Requests (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 358, Folder 5)
    - Requests (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 358, Folder 6)
    - Requests (1 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 358, Folder 7)
    - Requests (2 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 358, Folder 8)
    - Requests (3 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Requests (4 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - Requests (1 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - Requests (2 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - Requests (3 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - Student Requests (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - Student Requests (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - Student Requests, 1978-1979 (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - Small Business, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1979 (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - Unemployment Compensation, Cost Equalization, 1979 (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (1 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (2 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 360, Folder 8)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (3 of 3), 1978-1981 (Box 361a, Folder 1)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 361a, Folder 2)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 361a, Folder 3)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 361a, Folder 4)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 361a, Folder 5)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 361a, Folder 6)
    - Veterans’ Affairs (4 of 4), 1981 (Box 361b, Folder 1)
    - Veterans’ Affairs, WWI Pension, 1980-1981 (Box 361b, Folder 2)
    - FY ‘79 Budget, 1978 (Box 361b, Folder 3)
    - Wild Animals, 1978-1979 (Box 361b, Folder 4)
    - Rail Transportation (1 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 361b, Folder 5)
    - Rail Transportation (2 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 361b, Folder 6)
    - Water Transportation, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - Roads, 1978 (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - Law Enforcement, 1978-1981 (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - Federal Budget (1 of 3), 1978-1980 (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - Federal Budget (2 of 3), 1978-1980 (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - Federal Budget (3 of 3), 1978-1980 (Box 362, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture (1 of 10), 1978-1981 (Box 362, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture (2 of 10), 1978-1981 (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture (3 of 10), 1978-1981 (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture (4 of 10), 1978-1981 (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture (5 of 10), 1978-1981 (Box 363, Folder 4)